&gt；&gt；steve kinney：结束的想法，建议和未来的研究。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Closing thoughts,
recommendations, and future research.
[大笑]嘿，记住这个提示，只要确保你的应用程序处于生产模式
[LAUGH] Hey, remember this tip, just
make sure your app is in production mode
无论这对您的框架意味着什么。
whatever that means for your framework.
因为在开发模式中会发生很多实际的事情
Cuz there's a lot of actual stuff
that happens in development mode that
让你的生活更轻松。
makes your life easier.
就像没有理由，我这么说是因为我不小心射中了我的
That like there is no reason and I say
this cuz like I have accidentally shoot my
自己的应用程序和开发[INAUDIBLE]之前。
own app and
development [INAUDIBLE] before.
我去参观了一个正在进行的制作，为什么它是橙色的？
I've gone to visit a production going,
why is it orange?
我找到了他，就像网络包下垂的顺序是错误的。
I got to him like order of
web pack flagging is wrong.
就像我在运行[INAUDIBLE]后对生产环境所说的那样。
Like I said to production
environment after I ran [INAUDIBLE].
所以[INAUDIBLE]已经知道所有的支票都被剥离了
So it was already [INAUDIBLE] knows
all the checks were stripped out and
那么我设置生产模式对吗？
then I set production mode right?
所以毫无疑问，这很重要
So definitely, it matters so
很多，对，值得再重复一遍。
much, right,
that it's worth repeating one more time.
所以是的，没有反应。
So yeah, doesn't react.
它占用了PropTypes，接受了所有有用的警告，
It takes up PropTypes,
takes all the helpful warnings,
不做绩效指标。
doesn't do performance metrics.
只是一般说来。
It's just generally speaking.
如果您认为在开发代码时存在性能问题。
And if you think you have a performance
problem as you're developing code.
首先为生产构建它，看看是否仍然有问题。
Build it for production first, and
see if you still have a problem.
我失去了我生命中的日子，我再也回不来了，
I have lost days of my life,
that I will never get back,
跟踪不存在的性能问题。
tracking down performance
problems that didn't exist.
它们只存在于发展中。
They only existed in development.
你去看看，他们不在那里，对吧？
You go and you look, and
they're not there, right?
这就是为什么我重复这个，因为不要那样，保持那些日子。
That's why I'm repeating this one, because
don't be like that, keep those days.
[笑]别下去。
[LAUGH] Don't go down.
我这里有伤疤组织给你。
I have the scar tissue here for you.
你没必要这么做。
You don't have to do this.
我已经说了够多次了
I'm saying this enough times so
在调试20分钟后，你会想，我是为生产而构建的吗？
that 20 minutes into debugging you'll
be like, have I built for production?
让我为生产而建，看看这是不是一件事。
Let me built for production and
see if that's a thing.
如果我能在某一时刻为一个人节省一小时
And if I can save one person
an hour at some point
我要把这整件事称为胜利。
I'm going to call this entire thing a win.
当您处于生产模式时，您可以看到它是橙色的。
You see it's orange when
you're in production mode.
当你在开发模式中处于橙色时，它是黑色的，
It's black when you are in
orange in development mode,
黑色生产模式。
black in production mode.
就像这个帮助一样，如果你点击它，就会出现错误信息。
Like with this help for
error message if you click on it.
不管你选择的框架是什么，
Whatever your framework of choice is,
很可能有一个像这样的不同的工具，只是确保你正在使用它。
likely has a different tool like this
just make sure that you're using it.
很酷，所以网络表现是一个巨大的话题，就像一个不只是一天的话题。
Cool, so web performance is a giant topic,
like more than a one-day topic.
还有很多事情我们今天没有谈到。
And there's a lot of things that
we didn't get to talk about today.
服务器端呈现就是JavaScript需要花费时间来解析的想法。
Server-side rendering is this idea that
your JavaScript takes time to parse.
腿部负荷需要时间。
It takes time to leg load.
如果你寄给他们一个常客，
What if you sent them a regular,
旧的HTML页面，然后你把其他东西都加载了吗？
old HTML page and
then you got everything else loaded?
现在，根据你的申请，
Now, depending on your application,
如果是纽约时报，你可以把内容发给他们，没问题。
if it's the New York Times you can
send them the content no problem.
如果是推特，那么你得弄清楚他们的时间线，
If it's Twitter, well you've got to
do some figuring out their timeline,
您需要在服务器端完成所有这些工作。
you need to do all of that server-side.
不同的框架对此有不同的级别支持。
Different frameworks have
different level support for this.
恩伯是第一个，我相信，角度和反应都有支持
Ember was one of the first, I believe,
Angular and React both have support for
例如，IT但骨干可能不会。
it but Backbone, for instance, might not.
因此，它可能是您可以使用或可能不使用的东西。
So it might be something you can use or
might not use.
图像性能，我们开玩笑说取出一兆字节的JPEG是
Image performance, we joked that
taking out a megabyte of JPEGs is
不如取出一兆字节的JavaScript那么好。
not as good as taking out
a megabyte of JavaScript.
但也可以取出一兆字节的JPEG图像。
But also taking out
a megabyte of JPEGs is good.
所以你可以看到Medium做了一些非常有趣的事情。
So you can see Medium does
really interesting things.
他们给你看了一个模糊的版本，真的很低的分辨率。
Where they show you a blurred out
version that's really low res.
然后当你滚动到那个部分，他们就会加载图像。
And then when you scroll to that
part then they load the image.
所以你不会马上把你的图片发到文章下面六页。
So you're not sending your images for like
six pages down the article immediately.
他们等待，直到您的滚动事件获得该图像，然后加载它。
They wait until your scroll event gets
that image and then they load it.
在那里你可以做很多很酷的事情。
There's a bunch of cool
stuff you can do there.
性能的最大瓶颈之一是Web字体。
One of the biggest bottlenecks
on performance is web fonts.
谁不喜欢好的网页字体，对吧？
Who doesn't love a good web font, right?
但他们可能是，你看过你什么都看不到的页面吗？
But they can be, you've seen the page
where you're seeing nothing?
在字体加载之前，这并不是很好。
Until the font loads, that's not great.
Chrome实际上有一些非常有趣的工具，基本上，
Chrome actually has some really
interesting tools, where it's basically,
你实际上可以有一个你说，嘿，这就是我想要的字体的设置。
you can actually have a setting where
you say, hey, this is the font I want.
但如果时间太长，就用另一种字体，比如乔治亚，
But if it takes too long,
just use this other font, like Georgia,
或者Helvetica之类的
or Helvetica, or whatever.
最后，我之前提到过进步的Web应用程序。
And then finally, I kinda mentioned this
before about progressive web applications.
我认为这绝对非常重要
I think it's definitely,
incredibly important and
有趣的领域仍然在Safari中出现。
interesting field that's
still emerging in Safari.
然后beta现在将支持服务工作者，因此，
And then beta will now support
the service worker and so,
是的，打乱了离线工作，可以在后台同步。
yeah having upset work offline
that can sync in the background.
在我找到更多东西的时候可以马上给你看一样东西
And can show you a thing
immediately while I find more stuff
也是令人难以置信的强大。
is incredibly powerful as well.
这本身就是一个两天的话题，所以
It was a two day topic in and
of itself, so
就像，很难挤进其他所有的东西中。
like, hard to also squeeze
in amongst everything else.
非常感谢。
Thank you so much.